<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="main_buttons_title">
        <item>Disclaimer</item>
        <item>Hints</item>
        <item>Studio</item>
        <item>Gallery</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="main_buttons_note">
        <item>Author of this app does not assume resposibility for usage of  the third-party images. Using this app, the user is obliged to adhere to the law and respect the copyright.</item>
        <item>In the process, the hints will appear. Press next or selected element to continue.</item>
        <item>In this window you are working with the image. Main tools are hidden behind three buttons.</item>
        <item>There you open the folders, view the images etc. Pressing and holding an element of gallery opens the additional actions. Access to the multimedia is required for it to work.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draw_main_buttons_title">
        <item>Open drawing</item>
        <item>Tools</item>
        <item>Saving drawing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draw_main_buttons_note">
        <item>Add an image or begin a new project. If you want to combine images then work from here.</item>
        <item>Tools for drawing editing. Some of them are active only under certain conditions.</item>
        <item>Save or share an image from the studio here.</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="draw_add_title">
        <item>Camera</item>
        <item>Collection</item>
        <item>Blank canvas</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draw_add_note">
        <item>Open a photo taken from the camera. Access to the camera is required for it to work.</item>
        <item>Get an image from the collection.</item>
        <item>Create blank canvas yourself.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="draw_save_title">
        <item>Share</item>
        <item>Save</item>
        <item>Save</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draw_save_note">
        <item>Share the image from the studio.</item>
        <item>Save the image in certain location. System explorer will appear. In case of absence of the required storage check out menu of the explorer, it might be hidden.</item>
        <item>Save the image in previous location.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="draw_tools_title">
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Zoom</item>
        <item>Move</item>
        <item>Cut</item>
        <item>Distort</item>
        <item>Text</item>
        <item>Fill</item>
        <item>Eraser</item>
        <item>Brush</item>
        <item>Dropper</item>
        <item>Go back</item>
        <item>Go forward</item>
        <item>Outline</item>
        <item>Delete the project</item>
        <item>Seal</item>
        <item>Swap</item>
        <item>Sew</item>
        <item>Delete the image</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draw_tools_note">
        <item>Settings window for the tools. Always active.</item>
        <item>Zoom. You can switch one of the three modes pressing on this button. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Move the image on the screen. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Select the area and cut it pressing there. Tags along the outline and in the center let you to adjust the selection. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Rotation, distortion. Switch between them is right there. Last mode resets everything. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Insert the text. Press here again, the settings window for the text will appear. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Fill by color, fill inside the outlined area. Active when there is an image in the studio.</item>
        <item>Solid eraser and with gradients. Switch them here. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Brush, three modes and stain. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Copy the colour from the drawing. Previous tool remains active. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Redo.</item>
        <item>Undo.</item>
        <item>Outline of the drawing. Useful when working with transparent canvas. When working with two, the colours of the outlines are different. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Deletes the project with all history. Active when an image is present in the studio.</item>
        <item>Allows some of the tools affect both images. Active when an additional image is present.</item>
        <item>Swapping the places of main and upper images. Active when an additional image is present.</item>
        <item>Combine two images into one. Upper crops along the outline of the main. Active when an additional image is present.</item>
        <item>Delete upper image. Active when an additional image is present.</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="collect_title">
        <item>Add folder</item>
        <item>Manage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="collect_note">
        <item>Add a folder in gallery. System explorer will appear. Choose a folder and if it has the images, then it will be added. In case of absence of the required storage check out menu of the explorer, it might be hidden.</item>
        <item>App management.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="collect_root_menu_title">
        <item>Additional settings</item>
        <item>Hide</item>
        <item>Share</item>
        <item>Delete</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="collect_root_menu_note">
        <item>Additional settings mode. Applicable to one folder. Leave it by pressing this button.</item>
        <item>Hide this folder.</item>
        <item>Share the contents of this folder.</item>
        <item>Delete the selected folder.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="collect_adapt_menu_title">
        <item>Additional settings</item>
        <item>Share</item>
        <item>Delete</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="collect_adapt_menu_note">
        <item>Additional settings mode.  Applicable to more than one images. Leave it by pressing this button.</item>
        <item>Share the selected images.</item>
        <item>Delete the selected images.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="addlyr_title">
        <item>Size</item>
        <item>Transparency</item>
        <item>Mirror</item>
        <item>Negative</item>
        <item>Black and white</item>
        <item>Open</item>
        <item>Back</item>
        <item>Close</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addlyr_note">
        <item>Big size of the image can affect the stability of the app. Here you can resize it.</item>
        <item>Degree of transparency.</item>
        <item>Mirror image.</item>
        <item>Image inversion. To cancel, click here.</item>
        <item>Switch to black and white mode. To cancel, click here.</item>
        <item>Send the image to the studio.</item>
        <item>Return to the source of the image.</item>
        <item>Close window.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="review_title">
        <item>View the image</item>
        <item>Edit</item>
        <item>Exit</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="review_note">
        <item>Image view with the option to leaf through. With this button you can share it.</item>
        <item>Send to the edit window and then open in the studio. Important! Opening the image from here begins a new project.</item>
        <item>Close the view mode.</item>


    </string-array><string-array name="creator_title">
    <item>Open</item>
    <item>Width</item>
    <item>Height</item>
    <item>Background colour</item>
    <item>Exit</item>

</string-array>
    <string-array name="creator_note">
        <item>Blank canvas mode. Open canvas in editor to send it to the studio.</item>
        <item>Set width.</item>
        <item>Set height.</item>
        <item>Open colour selector. Press on center to exit.</item>
        <item>Close blank canvas mode.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="addlyr_collect_title">
        <item>Gallery</item>
        <item>Exit</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addlyr_collect_note">
        <item>Gallery contains folders with images. Open them in the studio. They will be added to the existing project. If studio already has an additional image then it will be replaced.</item>
        <item>Close the gallery.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="addlyr_cam_title">
        <item>Take a picture</item>
        <item>Camera selection</item>
        <item>Lightning</item>
        <item>Exit</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addlyr_cam_note">
        <item>Take a picture and open it in the editor.</item>
        <item>Choose which camera to use.</item>
        <item>Turn on the lightning.</item>
        <item>Close camera.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prop_title">
        <item>Brush</item>
        <item>Eraser</item>
        <item>Text</item>
        <item>Colour</item>
        <item>Brush transparency</item>
        <item>Width</item>
        <item>Eraser transparency</item>
        <item>Apply</item>
        <item>Exit</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prop_note">
        <item>Shows the brush. Its size and the colour.</item>
        <item>Eraser, width and level of erasing.</item>
        <item>Size and colour of the text.</item>
        <item>Set the colour of the brush and text.</item>
        <item>Set the transparency level of the selected colour.</item>
        <item>Set the width of the brush, eraser and size of the text.</item>
        <item>Adjust level of erasing.</item>
        <item>Apply the selected settings.</item>
        <item>Cancel and exit.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="edit_text_title">
        <item>Enter the text</item>
        <item>Cleanup</item>

        <item>Font</item>
        <item>Outline</item>
        <item>Angle</item>
        <item>Inclination</item>

        <item>Apply</item>
        <item>Exit</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="edit_text_note">
        <item>Text box.</item>
        <item>Delete previous text.</item>
        <item>Used font. Сlick to view list.</item>
        <item>Choose solid font or its outline.</item>
        <item>Adjust the angle of the font.</item>
        <item>Set the required inclination of the font.</item>
        <item>Save the changes and leave.</item>
        <item>Leave without changes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="edit_text_fonts_title">
        <item>List of the fonts</item>
        <item>Add a font</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="edit_text_fonts_note">
        <item>List of the available fonts.</item>
        <item>Add downloaded font. Font is a file with "ttf" or "otf" extension.</item>
    </string-array>





</resources>